EDIKURNIAWAN

Web Developer

ABOUT ME

I am a hard worker with experience as a web developer. I love coding so I study every day to improve my skills regarding web development. My experience is related to web development for about 1 year using several technologies to build websites from clients such as React and Laravel

PHONE

+62 813 5040 0660

EMAIL

edikurniawan.dev@gmail.com

PERSONAL WEBSITE

https://edikurniawan-dev.github.io/

LINKEDIN

https://www.linkedin.com/in/edikurniawan27

GITHUB

https://github.com/edikurniawan-dev

SKILLS

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

Python

PHP Git

TailwindCSS

ReactJS

NodeJS

Laravel

WordPress

Elementor

MySQL

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Informatics with GPA 3.38 of 4.00, Institut Teknologi Sumatera August 2017 - July 2021

EXPERIENCE

Frontend Web Developer at PT. Banopolis Inovasi Kendara

June 2020 - July 2020

Technologies: HTML, Bootstrap, JavaScript, SweetAlert

Develop the Jaramba Admin Dashboard display which functions to monitor the location of the bus that is running. In addition it stores route data, driver, bus and bus trip history

Computer Lab Assistant at Institut Teknologi Sumatera

February 2019 - November 2020

Technologies: HTML, CSS, JavaScript, C++, Excel, Linux

Teaches basic courses in Web Programming, Introduction to Computers and Software 2 and Operating Systems

PROJECTS

Privacy Guard Clone - Face Detection and Recognition Program

Technologies: Python, MobileNet-SSD, Keras, TensorFlow

- Develop a program to detect and recognize the laptop owner's face to maintain privacy by using a webcam
- The program will minimize the entire application if it detects another face and will display it again if there is only the face of the laptop owner

Peduli Panti - Web Application (BackEnd Developer)

Technologies: Laravel, Laravolt, MySQL

- Develop the login, register and forget password sections.
- Develop post and dashboard sections using MySQL database
- Using laravolt for data on all villages in Indonesia

Pelita Bersatu and An-Nazhori - Web Application (FrontEnd Developer)

Technologies: WordPress, Elementor

- Develop Home, Articles and more views using Elementor
- Develop website fully responsive

EVE-Store - Web Application (FrontEnd Developer)

Technologies: MongoDB, ExpressJS, ReactJS, NodeJS

Develop responsive website display using ReactJS

ORGANIZATIONAL EXPERIENCE

Secretary at Division Kemitraan dan Kerjasama in Generasi Baru Indonesia (GenBI) 2019 - 2020

Video Editor at Division Kreasi Dakwah Madani in Mahasiswa Peradaban Islam (Madani) 2018 - 2020

Public Relations at Himpunan Pelajar Matematika (HIPATIKA) SMAN 2 Kotabumi 2016 - 2017